Curriculum Vitae



Vũ Văn Đông







25/279 Tran Khat Chan Hai Ba Trung Ha Noi

01659672536

facebook.com/vvdongkthd

vuvandonghd94@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE

Short term/ 3- 6 months: Seeking a MR position with a good company on a long term basis who is looking for an experienced, hardworking, detail oriented team player.

Long term/ 5- 6 years: My goal is to become a sales manager and to partake in the growth and success of company I work for.



HOBBIES



Hi, my name is Dong. I'm currently a Sales Trainee at MSD

EDUCATION

 Aug 2012- Aug 2017: Ha Noi University of Pharmacy GPA: 2.81

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2015- Dec 2015: Former support staff at Sysdo VietNam

- Assist in organizing lessons and training English to students.
- Assist in organizing event such as Breaking Time and Team Building.
- Achievements: Contribute nearly 2000 candidates each generation. Improve English skills and also communication, time management skills.

Aug 2016- Dec 2016: Medical Representative at Cysina Traditional Trading Company

Achievements: Learn more about the product information, market, observe, learn and catch customers' taste well. Maintain about 40 drugstores to sale in territory.

Aug 2017- Now: Sales Trainee at MSD

Achievements: Learn how to manage territory, make plan, manage time. Learn how to make a call, handle objection, Q&A skill, presentation; understanding and presenting a clinical trial.

SKILLS

Problem solving

Microsoft Office

Communication skill

Teamwork